The reason why I'm mad is because
I am the exact man
that my father raised me to be.
And then I get grown
and they tell me
that this kind of [\h__\h] is toxic.
>> [laughter]
>> What do you mean toxic, [\h__\h] Like Like
I'm that blue bottle on the god damn
shelf. If you drink this, it's going to
kill everybody.
I'm poisonous.
All I am is the exact grown man that my
daddy raised me to be. I'm from the
south. I'm from Texas. What the hell do
you mean?
But then I did my research
and it dawned on me
that all the ladies
love that toxic [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, you do, [\h__\h] Yes, you do.
>> [cheering]
>> Yes, the [\h__\h] you do. That That [\h__\h] is
cute until it don't WORK FOR YOU.
OH, Y'ALL BE ACTING LIKE Y'ALL GOT
woman's intuition.
Well, where was your spider sense when
you shook his hand? It didn't tell you
that he beat [\h__\h] when you
When he said, "Hey, how you doing? I'm
Stephon." You
Did nothing tingle? Ooh, he whoop holes.
Like
No, that [\h__\h] was cute when y'all first
going together and [\h__\h] He
He whooped the [\h__\h] for accidentally
bumping into you at the club and [\h__\h]
She was like, "Ooh, my [\h__\h] will fight
for me."
>> [laughter]
>> Then when he at your cousin wedding
tearing your uncle ass up
cuz he pinched you on the booty. Uncle
called, "Hey, BABY GIRL, PINCHED YOU ON
YOUR BOOTY." THAT [\h__\h] STOLE THAT WHOLE
[\h__\h] WEDDING UP.
AND YOU LIKE, "STEPHON, OH MY
[screaming] GOD!"
CUZ YOU LIKE THAT toxic [\h__\h]
Y'all been liking that toxic [\h__\h] my
whole pubescent life.
I'm 36. Do your math. That mean I was
born in '85. That mean I entered puberty
in '96. I was 11.
Jodeci was a hot ass group.
>> [laughter]
[cheering and applause]
>> All through the '90s, Jodeci was a hot
ass group. All while I was 8 to 11
coming up. All little boys watch our
older cousins or older brothers if you
got them and you watch how they
co-mingle and coexist with the female
existence.
You see what they do.
You listen to the songs.
You peep the movements. You mimic their
maneuvers.
And Jodeci was one of the coldest
groups.
And y'all remember they was standing in
the desert.
And they dropped one of the coldest
songs ever
called Cry for You.
And every woman was like, "Yes, [\h__\h]
Cry for me."
And it was all four of them.
K-Ci, JoJo, DeVante, and Mr. Dalvin.
K-Ci was out there.
Blue jean vest, no shirt.
Cut off jeans.
Jodeci boots.
>> [laughter]
>> We don't even know what kind of boots
they was, but they was
Jodeci boots.
And K-Ci proceeded to sing out loud. He
said,
"It's been an hour since you've been
gone.
>> [cheering]
>> And that's too long. Come back home.
Can't live without you."
And they never done on y'all that that
[\h__\h] said 60 minutes had elapsed and
that was too [\h__\h] much time.
>> [laughter]
>> And that you needed to come your ass
back the [\h__\h] home. A hour?
A hour? Can't see that's too long.
Y'all like that toxic [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> You know who the most toxic [\h__\h] ever
was?
Michael Jackson.
Michael Joseph Jackson.
All his songs was toxic.
Mike out here getting side coochie
telling everybody.
I met this [\h__\h] at the club. I pulled
her down on the street.
I pulled the [\h__\h] in the car. She
grabbed the mic on me.
>> [laughter]
>> That ain't really what he said, but I'm
paraphrasing.
>> [cheering]
>> That [\h__\h] Mike was so toxic he
witnessed a murder and wouldn't say
nothing.
Yeah, that was the other song. Won't you
hush and let me tell the jokes?
>> [cheering and applause]
>> Oh, I want TO PARTICIPATE. I KNOW HE
TALKING ABOUT. FACE ASS.
>> [laughter]
>> But the next joke song was
Smooth Criminal.
Where he witnessed a murder and would
not say nothing.
Type of creepy ass [\h__\h] stand there and
watch a woman get murdered and won't say
nothing. And And I came up on the
window.
I heard [laughter] a sound down
on the kitchen door.
It came out of your apartment.
I see some blood stains on the carpet.
He going to lean all up in her window.
Annie, are you okay?
Are you okay? WHAT THE WON'T YOU CALL
911?
CREEPY ASS LITTLE BOY.
>> [cheering]
>> But the most TOXIC SONG OF ALL.
MICHAEL HAD GOT SOME COOCHIE from a lady
one night, one evening. They had a
beautiful time together.
And then that lady moved on with her
life.
Got married.
Married a rich [\h__\h] from Africa.
He took her back to Wakanda or Zamunda
or somewhere nice
like that. Had built her a brand new
palace.
But like most women, she still wasn't
satisfied.
She sitting over there bored.
He don't know what to do to entertain
her. He say, "What must I do?"
So he start doing little talent shows at
the house.
>> [laughter]
>> Start inviting all kind of [\h__\h] over
to the house.
Jugglers,
swallow eaters.
You know them [\h__\h] that be swallowing,
eating [\h__\h] Five swords. Swallow
eaters.
Magicians and [\h__\h] None of them [\h__\h]
would entertain this lady. She still was
not amused. Nine different [\h__\h]
performed.
Then the 10th [\h__\h] showed up. He wasn't
even on the list.
Magic Johnson didn't even know what to
call him. He was like, "And now
this nigga."
And this [\h__\h] walked out in front of
this lady and her brand new husband, all
on these people's brand new floor.
Opened up a bag of dirt and poured it
all on these people's brand new palace
floor.
And walked the [\h__\h] off.
And they was like, "HEY, WHAT YOU GOING
TO DO ABOUT THIS DIRT?" AND MICHAEL SPUN
his toxic ass out the dirt.
Do you remember?
And she immediately recognized Michael.
That's why she looked the [\h__\h] off.
Like, "I know Michael ass."
>> [laughter]
>> Ain't here talking about that one time
we [\h__\h] That one time
at my brand new house in front of my
husband.
And she ignored Mike for the whole
[\h__\h] song.
But Mike would not be ignored.
Who jumped out the dirt with him? All
the background dancers. Mike had
receipts. Ah.
Mike started NAMING PLACES. DO YOU
REMEMBER ON THE PHONE
AFTER [screaming] DARK
IN THE PARK
YOU AND ME
TWO OR THREE?
OR WHAT ABOUT
OR WHAT ABOUT [screaming] THAT THAT IS
WHEN HE ATE THE [\h__\h]
THAT THAT THAT
I'M BLACK, RON. GOOD NIGHT.
>> [cheering]
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
PROGRESSION OF SEX, like
these kids these DAYS JUMP STRAIGHT TO
THE
IT'S LEVELS TO THIS.
>> [laughter]
>> Who remember when kissing was Who
remember?
>> [cheering]
>> WHO REMEMBER?
>> [applause]
>> BOY, LITTLE KIDS GETTING OUT IN THE
STREETS. THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN ALL OVER
THE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, LIKE Wendy
Williams gossip.
No sooner you get off the bus, guess
what? What? Tyrone and Keisha was under
the bleachers. KISSING. WHAT?
And your HEART WOULD BE BROKEN.
Cuz how could you How could KEISHA KISS
ANOTHER [\h__\h] LIKE THAT?
[\h__\h] HOE ALL UNDER THE BLEACHERS.
KISSING ANOTHER [\h__\h] MAN.
AND I GAVE THAT HOE MY CANDY.
>> [laughter]
>> SOME OF Y'ALL WONDERING WHY A [\h__\h] LIKE
WHO HURT YOU? KEISHA BACK IN FIFTH
GRADE, [\h__\h]
IT AIN'T EVEN ABOUT YOU. GOD DAMN ME.
This trauma is deep seated.
We moved straight from KISSING TO ON TOP
OF THE BRA titty touching.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to say it again slow, on top
of the bra titty touching.
That's when you WENT UNDER THE SHIRT.
But she was raised IN A TWO PARENT
HOUSEHOLD, SO you had to stay on top of
the bra.
You touched your titty a little bit.
Went home with your hand just full of
pre-pubescent titty.
>> [laughter]
>> By the time you got to eighth grade,
it's time to take things up another
notch.
It's time to go on here and get the
fingering.
Cuz your cousin he was a early bloomer,
he had been fingering.
This [\h__\h] come over to the house with
enough DNA to be a god damn sexual
assault
suspect under his god damn thumbnail and
and middle finger.
And will present the evidence to you,
smell this.
>> [cheering]
>> AND LIKE A DOPE FIEND, YOUR ASS IS LIKE
MHM, WHAT IS THAT?
>> [cheering]
>> WHO IS THAT? THAT SMELL REMINISCENT. I
KNOW.
So we was WE WAS SOMMELIER'S FOR THAT
YOUNG COOCHIE.
It's a hint of Dove soap and
I'm smelling hints of oak and
elderberry.
And it was a it was a I was a whole task
to finger you some coochie back then.
Cuz the jeans was tall.
Big jeans, god damn. Them jeans way up
here, long zipper on them damn jeans.
Don't let her have on no button flies.
[\h__\h] you might not never get to that
damn promised land.
Cuz you had to have grown man hands
to undo the damn buckles on some
button-fly damn jeans. You
get through unfastening three of them
WWF turnbuckles.
>> [laughter]
>> Finally get them damn pants loose.
What's waiting on you? Some tall drawers
right up under that [\h__\h]
Big drawers. God damn it. WWF SummerSlam
drawers. They weighed above the I'MMA
TELL YOU SOMETHING, BROTHER. WHEN I GET
YOU IN THEM LEATHER MITTS, BROTHER, TYPE
DRAWERS.
YOU GOT TO BE THE INTERCONTINENTAL
Champion to get off in them god damn
drawers.
>> [applause]
>> You finally get down past them drawers
and there was a whole bunch of coochie
hair waiting on your ass.
Yes, it was. Wasn't it a bunch OF
COOCHIE HAIR?
DRY, COARSE, 4C coochie hair
waiting on your ass.
With no ass control on it or nothing.
With no leave-in conditioner in it or
nothing. Just
straight from the motherland.
>> [laughter]
>> Coochie hair waiting upon you.
You got your damn hand wet.
>> [cheering]
>> You got through them drawers and past
them pants and through that whole bush.
By the time you got to the spot and your
hand dry, you got TO COME BACK OUT.
REAPPLY.
AND THEN GO BACK DOWN the trail you had
just blazed for yourself.
AND THAT WAS SUCCESS.
THAT was a great night. You went home
with carpal tunnel and was like, "Yeah.
Did that."
But you didn't know that them was going
to be skills that you later on in your
grown man-dom, when you become
somebody's daddy.
They didn't drop something in the sink.
Your ass can take two fingers and get
off in that damn drain with your eyes
closed and pull the earring back out
that [\h__\h] like
"Damn daddy, where you get them MacGyver
skills?" Eighth grade, don't worry about
it.
Ain't no woman waiting on no dude to do
a whole ass thing in life. They're not
even waiting on you to die. They will
hurry up and get you there.
That's what hospice is, [\h__\h] That is a
hospital for [\h__\h] that ain't died yet.
Just need to go in there and lay him
down on his side and keep rotating him
till he going to get out of here.
Nobody put their mama in hospice. No,
you put your daddy in hospice, god damn
it. Your mama come live in in the back
room with children [\h__\h] You check on
your mama.
Your daddy, you don't even take him to
the facility. You let the people come
get his ass.
Nobody give a [\h__\h] about their daddy.
Y'all don't. Y'all don't give a damn
about y'all daddy.
Ain't nobody ever said, "Nigga, I'll
kill everybody in here AND THAT'S ON MY
DADDY." AIN'T NOBODY EVER said that.
Ain't nobody ever put it on their daddy.
You ain't never put that [\h__\h] on your
daddy, [\h__\h] But on your mama though,
on your mama, [\h__\h]
You ain't never seen a [\h__\h] win a whole
championship
and get on the camera and be like, "Hey
daddy."
You never seen a [\h__\h] win a BET award
and be like, "I want to thank God and my
daddy."
Never.
Niggas' daddies Niggas' daddies are up
there with like
middle school teachers.
We can only serve as a [\h__\h]
inspiration for a [\h__\h] that blew up who
wasn't supposed to be [\h__\h] in life, like
Yeah, know, daddy never loved me, my
teacher never said I was going to be
[\h__\h] Like them two them two positions
right there is the same.
My father walked out on me. I wasn't
good in social studies. Aren't them the
same?
I I I want to meet these teachers that
was really talking to [\h__\h] and
telling them that they wasn't going to
be [\h__\h] in life. Like
What type of bonafide educational worker
is this that was like, "You know you you
ain't going to be [\h__\h] in life.
Go to lunch." Like what?
This for all my teachers that told me I
wasn't going to amount to anything.
[\h__\h] if they all told you they was not
lying. [\h__\h] you was you was up there
bullshitting in them damn hallways.
Skipping school smelling like tater tots
and [\h__\h] You was up at that school
[\h__\h] off.
And you hit a lick.
You the only [\h__\h] that can rhyme words
with orange and you [\h__\h] around.
Dumbest picture I ever seen in my whole
[\h__\h] life during the quarantine. It's
a rapper, his name MoneyBagg Yo. Y'all
might have heard of He say, "I don't
like [\h__\h] I don't like [\h__\h] I
don't like nobody." Will you get your
antisocial ass
You go home, sir.
He got a picture out.
He got like 19 cars parked behind him.
All of them different makes and models.
They all got the same
paint scheme.
They all red on black.
And the caption said
I got all F's on my report card.
You said that [\h__\h] like that was
something to be proud of, sir.
You got all F's on your report card
like, "Yeah, they said I wasn't going to
be nothing, but now look.
You know who [clears throat] got all A's
on their report card?
Everybody who see they your check before
you get it, dumbass boy, like your
agent, the record company, your manager,
the radio people, the all the [\h__\h] who
painted the trucks red and black for
your stupid ass.
Don't you know he got a A in truck
painting, dumbass boy?
I got all F's on my report card. I blame
you new parents for that [\h__\h]
Y'all didn't talk these kids that you
ain't got to win in life to be a winner.
I'm a 80's baby. The only way your ass
got a pizza party was if you sold the
most candy bars, read the most books,
or your team won a championship, god
damn it.
[\h__\h] if y'all didn't win, you didn't
get no personal pan for your defeat,
stupid ass boy.
Losers get tuna fish sandwiches, winners
get pizza. What the [\h__\h] are you talking
about?
We used to have to shake team shake
hands with the [\h__\h] who had just
kicked our ass. They call that [\h__\h] good
sportsmanship. We all had to line up and
tell them good game, good game, good
game. You kicked my ass, good game, good
game. You dunked on me, good game, way
to go.
They don't do that [\h__\h] now. Everybody
just take off running and go back to
their damn locker rooms and [\h__\h]
Like when I was coming up,
the word no
didn't inflict nobody at home.
So like when we would holler at women,
she said no, cool, hey, how you doing?
Hey man, God bless you. You single? No,
all right, well [\h__\h] you too. Hey man,
how you doing? God bless you, all right,
cuz I know before I get through asking,
somebody in this [\h__\h] club
going to dance with me.
Rejection don't hurt.
These [\h__\h] these days ain't never
been rejected.
A woman tell them no, he'll just block
her ass on Instagram,
create a new profile, shadow follow her
ass.
These the same [\h__\h] that be shooting
up public places and [\h__\h] cuz they ain't
never heard no. Like, "Yeah, I can get
the phone number?" Hell no, you ugly
ass.
I'll be right back, [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Finna come wet this hole up when I come
back in here.
You won't SAY NO TO ME?
I DON'T EVEN LIKE YOUNG SEXY HOES.
I don't even know how to be as young and
sexy.
I like me a grown ass woman.
Don't give me no visual apostrophe in
her name.
Got a L and a K right next to each other
and [\h__\h]
I don't need that. Give me a Earnestine.
Hell yeah, [\h__\h] And she grown, so you
call her Miss Earnestine, god damn it,
with respect.
Young sexy hoes, they be thinking they
got like matching bra and panties.
They think that's sexy.
Not Miss Earnestine.
Miss Earnestine got matching dishes,
[\h__\h] That's sexy.
When the plate go with the saucer, go
with the teacup.
Let me open your cabinets and all your
dishes match, [\h__\h] I'm ready to bust
on right then, god damn it.
It's one word, bust on. F U T T S U M M.
Say it with me, church. Bust on. Hell
yeah. I'm ready to bust on.
Soon as I get over Miss Earnestine's
house cuz she make a [\h__\h] feel
comfortable.
>> [laughter]
>> And my dick get hard for comfort these
days.
Don't know what make me want to bust on.
Like a little comfort, god damn it. Let
me pull up and you got a driveway,
garage, carport situation. I'm ready to
bust on right then.
Somebody know six [\h__\h] ain't going to
be chilling on my [\h__\h] when I get back
outside. Make me comfortable.
Soon as I get in your
this little [\h__\h] make me want to bust
something.
Let me SEE SOME LAMPS.
>> [laughter]
>> REAL LAMPS, [\h__\h] PLURAL, LAMPS.
I'm ready to bust something right then.
You know what? If you have lamps, you
got to have end tables.
>> [laughter]
>> Look at the young hoes like, "What's an
end table? What the [\h__\h] is he talking
about?"
Grown [\h__\h] in here like, "And two,
two of them."
>> [laughter]
>> One for each of them lamps, god damn it.
Look at young sexy hoes that got lamps,
plural. She got a lamp,
singular, [\h__\h] That one smooth
criminal leaning ass lamp.
In her bedroom, [\h__\h] That hoe got a
wig and a work badge hanging off of it.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> Go to them young sexy hoes' house, boy,
you'll be struggling [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
That's what I call it.
Cuz they looking good, but they doing
bad, [\h__\h] You
>> [laughter]
>> You have to struggle [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
You don't go to young hoes' sexy hoes'
house, you'll eat some cereal. Just
basic [\h__\h] some cereal.
She put the cereal in a god damn
spaghetti bowl that got red ring around
it and [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> You eating cereal. You got a damn spoon
so weak, [\h__\h] it be in like in the
Matrix.
You just eating cereal, [\h__\h] You got a
damn weak ass Dollar Tree ass spoon.
[\h__\h] IS OKAY, HOLD NO 100 MONSTER OATS,
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> NO MISUNDERSTANDING, [\h__\h] HELL NO.
Misunderstanding silverware made out of
Valyrian steel, [\h__\h] She got that god
damn
>> [cheering]
>> GAME OF THRONES 300 ASS SILVERWARE,
[\h__\h] You'll be sitting at the table
speaking, [\h__\h] and after [laughter] I
sup, I SHALL FEAST UPON THEE.
>> [laughter]
>> LET ME GO IN YOUR HOUSE AND YOU GOT THEM
GOD damn Glade PlugIns.
Let you have a different scent in every
room. [\h__\h] I'm talking about to bust
something. You got apple cinnamon in the
bathroom, ocean sea breeze in the
kitchen, [\h__\h] You got pumpkin spice in
your bedroom. I'm talking about [\h__\h]
something right there.
RIGHT THERE. YOUNG SEXY HOES AIN'T GOT
GLADE PLUG-INS. THEY GOT FABULOSO ON THE
BACK OF THE STOVE.
Purple and some water.
GOT A LITTLE WATER AND THEY GOT THAT
FABULOSO.
>> [laughter]
>> Fumigating that whole goddamn project
ass apartment.
Ain't nobody talking about [\h__\h]
nothing right there.
>> [laughter]
>> Don't even invite you to the room sexy.
They be like, "Come on, my kids sleep."
They going to [\h__\h] something.
>> [laughter]
>> No, [\h__\h] How my dick ain't going to
get hard for no my kids sleep?
Miss Understanding just spoiled me,
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Miss Understanding let the whole picture
go off. That's what she call a movie, A
PICTURE.
MISS UNDERSTANDING LET THAT GODDAMN
PICTURE go off, [\h__\h]
Let the credits roll, [\h__\h]
Dim the lights, lean over to me, "Young
man,
you ready to retire TO THE BOUDOIR?"
YES, I AM, [\h__\h] Let us retire this
evening.
Right now today.
Ready to retire.
Only one drawback to [\h__\h] with Miss
Understanding.
See, she don't have sex with enthusiasm
like them young sexy hoes do.
Young sexy hoes cut a album in the bed.
Boy, that would be Grammy nominated,
don't it?
>> [laughter]
>> Young sexy hoes, "Oh my god, I think I'm
about to come.
Oh my god, I think I'm about to come.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my [\h__\h] god, I think I'm ABOUT TO
COME.
I THINK I'M ABOUT TO COME.
OH MY [\h__\h] GOD,
>> [laughter]
>> I think I'm about to come.
You hear the hoe? "Oh my [\h__\h] god, I
think I'm about to come. I think I'm
about to [\h__\h] come.
Oh my [\h__\h] god, I think I'M ABOUT TO
COME."
>> [laughter]
>> NOW, MISS UNDERSTANDING.
>> MISS UNDERSTANDING BE COMING IN
DISBELIEF.
She be
"Mhm, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> [cheering]
[screaming]
>> WELL, I'LL BE DAMNED.
I know you [\h__\h] lying.
[\h__\h] go ahead then, boy.
Go young sexy ho, you can fold them up,
[\h__\h] You can fold her young sexy ass
up, [\h__\h] Pool chair, [\h__\h] Fresh
laundry, fold up.
Do [laughter] you like this, coochie?
I'm laying up like this.
Now, now Miss Ernestine, you got to be
gentle.
Can't throw Miss Ernestine all across
that bed like that.
Oh, oh, slow down, young man. Take your
time now.
You [\h__\h] Miss Ernestine, she be like
"Uh-uh, baby, put that leg down. That
hip ain't no good."
>> [cheering]
>> Ain't no good, [\h__\h] WHAT THAT HIP
EXPIRED? THAT HIP AIN'T NO GOOD, BABY.
IF YOU BE QUIET, YOU CAN HEAR THAT HIP
CLICK, [\h__\h] THAT HIP BE in there
I already TOLD YOU THEM YOUNG SEXY HOES,
THEY CUT A ALBUM off in there.
You get to hit that spot, YOUNG GIRL, BE
>> [screaming]
>> "WHAT YOU DOING TO ME? I'M A
SOUND LIKE ANIME CHARACTERS.
SOUND LIKE SHE DYING ON STREET FIGHTER.
YOU BE RIGHT WITH HER.
>> [screaming]
>> YOU DYING ON STREET FIGHTER WITH HER
ASS.
YOU GOT TO PUT another quarter in you
want to keep going.
Not Miss Ernestine, [\h__\h] Hell no.
Miss Ernestine come, [\h__\h] she sound
like a old [\h__\h] falling down the
stairs.
MISS ERNESTINE BE LIKE
"OH, YOUNG UH OH.
OH, YOU OH.
OH, YOU'RE KILLING [screaming] ME. OH.
OH. OH.
OH, NOT LIKE THAT.
OH.
AGAIN? YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT AGAIN?
HEY, MAN, I'm black RONALD [\h__\h]
REAGAN.
>> [cheering]
>> WHAT'S UP WITH IT, Y'ALL? WE HERE. WE
OUTSIDE WITH IT. We made it.
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah.
WE SURVIVED.
AIN'T NOBODY GOT NO MASK ON.
Look at y'all. Corona died. We didn't
have no funeral for Corona or nothing.
We just moved on with our lives. We just
went right back. [\h__\h] the social
distance. We back.
>> [laughter]
>> I missed breath.
Cuz like for the whole quarantine, I've
been talking to people, their breath
wasn't hitting my face.
The masks was in the way and [\h__\h]
I forgot how hot and aggressive breath
can be. I had
Some [\h__\h] like they got bad
breath. They don't have a bad breath
face. They look regular faced and like
regular teeth brushing people and [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> I was so happy to be outside. I was just
hugging people and talking face to face.
[\h__\h] [clears throat] grabbed me
by my shoulder.
He started talking.
Inside his whole chest was dead.
[laughter]
Cuz all through the quarantine, I've
just been talking to people for a long
ass time.
Breath let you wrap up the conversation
and [\h__\h] [laughter]
You smell that breath, you thinking of
some [\h__\h] to do. Ooh, [\h__\h] left the
stove on. I got to go get my kids. All
right, I'll see you later. I'll see you
later on.
The mask was on, you was just talking.
Tell me about [laughter] your life. Man,
what happened? Oh, you're teaching your
own kids. That's good. Hell yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Really [\h__\h] you up when you catch a girl
with that breath.
Cuz you had forgot. You know, you had
been seeing ladies. You had just been
You've been single through this
quarantine.
Romance went out the window. Ain't ain't
no more dating dating. Ain't no more
getting to know nobody. Hell no.
Couldn't go no damn where. Everything
was closed.
Couldn't go to no restaurant.
They drop your food off at the door like
it's a bomb and back [laughter] away
from that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] will put your freshly
bought food on the [\h__\h] floor.
>> [applause]
>> Knock on your door, run the [\h__\h] off.
You
You over THERE OUTSIDE JUST SOME CHICK
OVER THERE WAITING on you outside and
[\h__\h]
They done ate two of your waffle fries.
You don't even know who to complain
>> [laughter]
>> You meet a young lady
she agree to come over
ain't no romance. Hell no. You get here,
I'm going to scan your forehead.
>> [cheering]
>> I I was the only one went and bought one
of them little guns off Amazon.
>> [laughter]
>> [\h__\h] and it and it better come back
orange every time, [\h__\h] Look at that
little doo-doo-doo. Oh, hell no. Get
your
Get your ass out of my house today,
right now.
Scan your forehead. I'm going to spray
you down just bleach water. You going to
come in here
You going to [\h__\h] with our masks on?
I'm going to put your ass out. Ain't no
snacks. Nope, I got you some almonds and
one of them little shark waters in this
little bag.
Get your ass on out of here. God bless
you and drive safe.
>> [laughter]
>> Ain't no romance.
>> You going to sit here and Netflix and
chill? Uh-uh.
[\h__\h] like to cough when they watch
movies. I don't know if y'all know that
or not. That's how a woman let you know
she getting comfortable, right? When she
lay on you, she go
Uh-huh, [\h__\h] Uh-huh, [\h__\h]
Uh-uh. [\h__\h]
The greasing went up, [\h__\h] Get out.
Get out.
Corona took away all our manners.
Used to have a good upbringing.
Somebody used to sneeze, what would you
say?
Bless you. You super saved, you say,
"God bless you."
>> [laughter]
>> Let somebody sneeze on your ass now.
Take that [\h__\h] as a direct sign of
disrespect. [laughter]
You just sitting there talking and [\h__\h]
I know you [\h__\h] lying to me.
IN FRONT [applause] OF MY BABY, [\h__\h]
UH, HELL NO.
First of all, why you AIN'T ON YOUR DOT?
AND WHAT THE DOT [\h__\h] WAS SOME [\h__\h]
WASN'T IT?
Especially when you respect the dot, you
know what I'm saying? [\h__\h] right
there, you 6 ft back, you on your dot.
You got both your feet together on the
dot.
And you feel wind, warm breath wind on
your neck.
[\h__\h] if I feel your wind, your mask
ain't on. I know that.
Turn around, you ain't on your damn dot.
We finna tear this [\h__\h] grocery store
up.
[\h__\h] I need 4 and 1/2 more feet of
space about you.
And the basket don't count, [\h__\h] That
supposed to be behind you.
I know but I just want the dot. YOU
DON'T WANT A goddamn thing but a
problem. If you don't want to scoot your
ass 4 and 1/2 more feet back.